[{"answer": "Yes, that very much is what people are doing.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "What was that and is that what people are doing to protect themselves?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "It looks similar, but it's actually more -- the parallels are closer to another set of scenes that you might remember.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Is it similar, though, or is it a very different kind of thing that what we're seeing right now in Istanbul?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I'm absolutely surprised.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "And what do you think has triggered it?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "It is clearly a miscalculation but the reason is I think he sees himself as very different.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Fareed, I mean, this prompts the question given what has happened to all the dictators in the Middle East in the last two years, why would Erdogan want to put himself into that kind of category by behaving in what appears to be a dictatorial manner?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Margaret Thatcher.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Margaret Thatcher?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "There are elements of Putinism here that certainly in the way the media has been treated in Turkey and the fact that my colleagues in the Turkish media are largely terrified of criticizing this prime minister and showing things that will make him angry and also the measures that have been taken against the big media owners in the country, slapping them with half billion-dollar tax fines has a certain way of changing the editorial tone of TV network.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Are we seeing that the Turkish Putin emerging here do you think?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I think it all depends.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "What will happen in the next few days and weeks do you think?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, I think so and I think that the behavior of the prime minister has become increasingly authoritarian as was said.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Are they right to be that concerned?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, what should happen, I guess, first of all, we have to -- we have to get him back under our jurisdiction and it's not clear to me how that's going to happen because he's half way around the world.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "How tough should the penalties be for him?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, I think we got to be absolutely clear that whenever the NSA wants to look into the content of communications of Americans, they've got to have a warrant.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Finally and briefly, if you don't mind, where do you see the line being drawn between an individual's right to privacy in America particular in the modern technological era with so much data available through computers and social networking and cell phones, and so on and a government, a state, a country's right to defeat and attack and take on terrorism through the kind of activities the NSA does?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "In terms of the reaction from various bodies, the State Department's response is, \"We hold all employees to the highest standards.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Were things that might turn into scandals just cut off midway?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I think it's cannon fodder for political shows and talk radio.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "How damaging could this be to her?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I think there's a couple of answers to that.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Is there anything that he's done except to warn the public interest?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "What do you see here with this guy?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Why is he a hero?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Robin, let me ask you.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Is that really what she is?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Yes, well, that is the big tradeoff.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What is to stop people with this kind of information doing exactly the same thing?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "That is a big --", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Kevin, there hasn't always been a good faith expectation from the American public.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Marc, Marc Lamont Hill, do you -- do you feel that, Marc Lamont Hill?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "You know, rating amongst the American public but we've seen poll after poll come out actually in the context of a very heated and emotional debate in the country where people have said in poll after poll that they are willing to give up some freedom for -- for security.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Robin?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "They -- as John Miller suggested, he could just be a bit of a loser, who was never a big achiever, who didn't go through all checks and balances, and thought I'm going to go out as some great hero.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Why didn't he go through the whistleblower program?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "A gazelle, I guess.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "(LAUGHTER) Robin, what do you hunt with a gun that can shoot from that far away?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "But you know what, if civilians could have that, I would be happy to know that our military has it.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Are there elephants in Texas that I'm not aware of?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yes, you could probably shoot the wings off a fly with that.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Kevin Madden?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "The right to bear arms means you have a right to bear a gun that can shoot from 10 football fields away and take down herds of elephants.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Kevin, you don't think that's OK, do you?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I really don't think he meant it as a joke.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Robin Meade, explain to me how he doesn't get any jail time for head butting his wife but he does get 30 days in jail for patting the backside of his attorney?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Everyone slaps their butts, right?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "This is absolutely ridiculous.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Justice completely turned on its face here?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "And she was about to let him out on probation, correct?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "About domestic violence?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Well, full disclosure, I'm a Cincinnati Bengals fan, so I used to be a big fan of Chad Johnson.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Why is he being jailed for triviality when he wasn't being jailed for head-butting his wife?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Are you -- are you brave enough to give me a few little bars now?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Gotcha.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Anything you like?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Thanks.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "But what is it about singing?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "IMMERMAN: Well, many attorneys will tell you that a case is won essentially in jury selection.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "How important is that going to be, do you think, for determining the outcome?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think George put on the weight because of the stress.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "I mean, how is he and why has he put on so much weight?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Well, I can't talk about George's regrets but I certainly --", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Does he regret now carrying a gun around now like that?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Do you regret that he had?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "I don't --", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "But do you actually think that Trayvon Martin was going to beat your brother to death?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I think that there has been discoverable evidence that's come forward that shows that Mr. Martin really enjoyed fighting.", "docId": "130611pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "I mean, is that really what you think would have happened in that case?", "qSentId": 607}]